<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<error-codes>
    <sect nr="2.2" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#charsets">
        <code id="2.2.2.0" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#dt-character">A character is an atomic unit of text as specified by ISO/IEC 10646:2000 [ISO/IEC 10646]. Legal characters are tab, carriage return, line feed, and the legal characters of Unicode and ISO/IEC 10646. [...] Consequently, XML processors MUST accept any character in the range specified for Char.</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="2.6" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#NT-PI">
        <code id="2.6.17.0" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#NT-PITarget">The target names " XML ", " xml ", and so on are reserved for standardization in this or future versions of this specification.</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="2.8" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#sec-prolog-dtd">
        <code id="2.8.29.2" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#wfc-PEinInternalSubset">In the internal DTD subset, parameter-entity references MUST NOT occur within markup declarations; they may occur where markup declarations can occur. (This does not apply to references that occur in external parameter entities or to the external subset.)</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="3" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#sec-logical-struct">
        <code id="3.0.39.1" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#GIMatch">The Name in an element's end-tag MUST match the element type in the start-tag.</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="3.1" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#sec-starttags">
        <code id="3.1.40.1" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#uniqattspec">An attribute name MUST NOT appear more than once in the same start-tag or empty-element tag.</code>
        <code id="3.1.41.2" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#NoExternalRefs">Attribute values MUST NOT contain direct or indirect entity references to external entities.</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="4.1" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#sec-references">
        <code id="4.1.68.1" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#wf-entdeclared">In a document without any DTD, a document with only an internal DTD subset which contains no parameter entity references, or a document with " standalone='yes' ", for an entity reference that does not occur within the external subset or a parameter entity, the Name given in the entity reference MUST match that in an entity declaration that does not occur within the external subset or a parameter entity, except that well-formed documents need not declare any of the following entities: amp, lt, gt, apos, quot. The declaration of a general entity MUST precede any reference to it which appears in a default value in an attribute-list declaration.</code>
        <code id="4.1.68.3" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#textent">An entity reference MUST NOT contain the name of an unparsed entity. Unparsed entities may be referred to only in attribute values declared to be of type ENTITY or ENTITIES.</code>
        <code id="4.1.68.4" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#textent">https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#norecursion</code>
        <code id="4.1.69.0" href="https://www.w3.org/TR/xml/#NT-PEReference">Parameter-entity references use percent-sign (%) and semicolon (;) as delimiters.</code>
    </sect>
    <sect nr="Errata-2e" href="https://www.w3.org/XML/xml-V10-2e-errata">
        <code id="E2e.38" href="https://www.w3.org/XML/xml-V10-2e-errata#E38">With the advent of XML 1.1, this clarifies that 1.0 documents may not refer to entities of versions other than 1.0.</code>
    </sect>
</error-codes>
